

CONTACT

+254715886551

Nairobi, Kenya

Web Development

Attention to Detail

Effective Communication

Critical Thinking & Problem

PHP, Python

Git, SQL

solving

Digital Marketing

English (Fluent)

• Kiswahili (Fluent)

REFERENCE

LANGUAGES

HTML, CSS, Java script

SKILLS

DOMINIC NJENGA

WEB DEVELOPER/ICT SUPPORT OFFICER

8

PROFILE

Am an experienced I.T professional with a history in different areas of information technology. I graduated with a Degree and Diploma in information technology. Have experience working with and on computers. I have Knowledge of Website Design, Graphic Design, and computer maintenance. I am a candidate ready to utilize years of experience in IT to excel in any position.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Lapsset Corridor Development Authority

2021 - 2022

Web Developer

- Ensure the website is fast, responsive, and optimized for performance.
- Perform regular updates and maintenance tasks such as adding new features, fixing bugs, and ensuring compatibility with the latest web standards and technologies.
- Continuously learn and adopt new web technologies, tools, and best practices to stay competitive and provide modern, efficient solutions.

Kenya Revenue Authority

2018 - 2019

ICT Officer Intern

- Taught end-users how to use Ms. Office Applications and other IT peripheral devices such as printers, scanners, and projectors.
- Installed applications and software e.g. SAP client, QPulse on user workstations.
- Troubleshoot network problems and faulty cables.

China Dalian International

2017 - 2017

ICT Support

- Computer hardware maintenance -installed new hardware devices such as hard drives, and new computer monitors.
- Data entry and data back-up- used Excel to key in data and calculations.



EDUCATION

Degree In Information Technology

2014 - 2017

Taita Taveta University
Second Upper Division

Diploma In Information Technology

2011 - 2013

Jomo Kenyatta University of Agriculture & Technology Credit

Oscar Lagat

Lapsset Corridor Authority **Phone:** 0712498453

Email: klagat@lapsset.go.ke

Martin Kibet

Kenya School of Tvet

Phone: 0721992906